During this lecture, we're going to use a few tools for different purposes.
We will connect to hardware with cellular link.
We will open SSH connection and we'll also send different kind of command from a terminal. For each demonstration,
we could have used many different tools and I'm sure some of you have your favorites.
Well, the content of this lecture is not to provide explanation in the tutorial style.
With this course for every demonstration, we will always explain what you absolutely need to know,
and we'll also provide one tool to do it.
It might not be your favorite one, but there won't be a big difference if you do it in another way.
MobaXterm is a tool that gathers everything we need for this lecture: SSH connection, sale
link connection, and a terminal to send commands.
So that's the one we'll use.
Unfortunately, it's only available for Windows.
If you work with the Linux operating system, it really doesn't matter and things should be really easy
anyway because there is many other options.
I will always propose some, but I'm sure that if you're using Linux, you are already familiar with them.
So to install MobaXterm toolbox, then you just need to go on the MobaXterm website, download
and install it.
If you don't want to install anything, there is also a portable edition of the software.
Both work perfectly.
Once MobaXterm is installed on your computer, then you're ready.
Nothing else is required for now.
For example.
When we need a terminal with some embedded Linux command.
Then we'll simply open it here.
When we'll use an SSH client or a cellular terminal, then we'll open an SSH session or a cellular session.
I'll let you play with this.
And anyway, I will explain this tool when we need them.